[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone. <br /><br />Click \"Continue\" when you're ready to move on.","rt":140240,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":146244,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6 </sub>,  you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":6560,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":152807,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":1268,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":154077,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5 "],"rt":2958,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":157036,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1102,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":158139,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":6126,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":164266,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":960,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":165229,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":16544,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":181775,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1050,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":182827,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum  is 6 or  bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3134,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":185963,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":918,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":186883,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":1943,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":188827,"internal_chunk_id":"0 -0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1023,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":189851,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2823,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":192675,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":908,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":193584,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, t o perfor m +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2034,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":195619,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":975,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":196595,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":2080,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":198676,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1198,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":199876,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":1913,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":201790,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":4081,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":205872,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":7009,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":212883,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the thing that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Simil arly, 3  is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":16905,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":229789,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":55080,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":284873,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1263,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":286139,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of a n elemen t is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":7994,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":294135,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":978,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":295115,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":4918,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":300034,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correc t! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":928,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":300963,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":3848,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":304812,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":888,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":305702,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br  /> (Rem ember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":2154,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":307856,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":4770,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":312628,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":10559,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":323188,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We  have one  last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because of this, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":173391,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":496580,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can m ake ever y other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":8891,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":505476,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":3038,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":508515,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":5279,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":513796,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a g enerator  under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":8686,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":522483,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":2671,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":525155,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</ sub> 4,  and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1190,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":526347,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":4929,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":531277,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":901,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":532179,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</su b>, on t he numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":6920,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":539100,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"9","response_history":["9"],"rt":3388,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":542491,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":4582,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":547076,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0 "},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":5206,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":552283,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3378,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":555663,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3515,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":559179,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2425,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":561605,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2091,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":563698,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5. Since 4 + 1 is less than 9, you leave the result alone","response_history":["5. Since 4 + 1 is ","5. Since 4 + 1 is","5. Since 4 + 1 i","5. Since 4 + 1 is less than 9, you leave the result of ","5. Since 4 + 1 is less than 9, you leave the result of","5. Since 4 + 1 is less than 9, you leave the result o","5. Since 4 + 1 is less than 9, you leave the result alone"],"rt":37825,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":601524,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3. Since 8 + 4 = 12, which >9, you subtract 9 from the result (12-9=3)","response_history":["3. Since 8 + $ ","3. Since 8 + $","3. Since 8 + 4 = 12, which >9, you subtract 9 from the result (12-9=3)"],"rt":31847,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":633373,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0, because you can add the inverse of a +9 number to get 0.","response_history":["0, because you can add the inverse of f","0, because you can add the inverse of a +9 number to get it.","0, because you can add the inverse of a +9 number to get 0."],"rt":341843,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":975220,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":7324,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":982549,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":2858,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":985411,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6. The identity is 0, and 6+3 = 9, which becomes 0 due to the +9 rule.","response_history":["6.  The identity is 0, and 6+3 = 9, which becomes 0 due to the +9 rule,","6. The identity is 0, and 6+3 = 9, which becomes 0 due to the +9 rule."],"rt":136534,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":1121948,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes, you can make every number using just 2 under +9","response_history":["Yes, you can make every number using just 2 under +9"],"rt":172962,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":1294914,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No, it's not possible to make any number that's not 0 or a multiple of 3 with just 3.","response_history":["No, it ","No, it's not possbile","No, it's not possbil","No, it's not possbi","No, it's not possb","No, it's not possible to make any number that's not 0 or a multiple of 3 with just 3."],"rt":65768,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":1360685,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No, you can't make several numbers with just a 5 under +9.","response_history":["No, you can't make several numbers with just a 5 under +9."],"rt":57257,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":1417943,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No, you can't make numbers other  than 3,  6, and 9 with just 6.","response_history":["No, you can't make numbers of","No, you can't make numbers other than 3, 6, and 9 ","No, you can't make numbers other than 3, 6, and 9.","No, you can't make numbers other than 3, 6, and 9 with just 6."],"rt":252725,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1670672,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use \"+_n\", and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":5151,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1675827,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":" n-1","response":"n-1","response_history":["n-1"],"rt":39098,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1714927,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"n-x. The inverse is the value that causes it plus x to equal n, which changes the result to 0 (the identity).","response_history":["n-x. The inverse id ","n-x. The inverse id","n-x. The inverse is the value that casue","n-x. The inverse is the value that casu","n-x. The inverse is the value that cas","n-x. The inverse is the value that causes it plus x to equal n, which changes tha","n-x. The inverse is the value that causes it plus x to equal n, which changes the result to 0 (the identity0","n-x. The inverse is the value that causes it plus x to equal n, which changes the result to 0  (the ide ntity)."],"rt":68477,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1783407,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"It seems like if x is odd and n is even (or vice-versa), then it is a generator. If both are odd or even, you usually only get elements that are multiples of x.","response_history":["If x is odd and n is even (or vice0","If x is odd and n is even (or vice-versa)","It x is odd and n is even (or vice-versa)","It n x is odd and n is even (or vice-versa)","It ns x is odd and n is even (or vice-versa)","It n x is odd and n is even (or vice-versa)","It  x is odd and n is even (or vice-versa)","It s x is odd and n is even (or vice-versa)","It se x is odd and n is even (or vice-vers a)","It  see x is odd and n is even (or vice-versa)","It seem x is odd and n is even (or vice-versa)","It seems x is odd and n is even (or vice-versa)","It seems  x is odd and n is even (or vice-versa)","It seems l x is odd and n is even (or vice-versa)","It seems li x is odd and n is even (or vice-versa)","It seems lik x is odd and n is even (or vice-versa)","It seems like x is odd and n is even (or vice-versa)","It seems like  x is odd and n is even (or vice-versa)","It seems like i x is odd and n is even (or vice-versa)","It seems like if x is odd and n is even (or vice-versa), then it is a generator. I both ","It seems like if x is odd and n is even (or vice-versa), then it is a generator. I both","It seems like if x is odd and n is even (or vice-versa), then it is a generator. I bot","It seems like if x is odd and n is even (or vice-versa), then it is a generator. I bo","It seems like if x is odd and n is even (or vice-versa), then it is a generator. I b","It seems like if x is  odd and  n is even (or vice-versa), then it is a generator. I ","It seems like if x is odd and n is even (or vice-versa), then it is a generator. If both are odd or even, you usually only get elements that are multiples of x."],"rt":276578,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":2059987,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":6965,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":2066955,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":3565,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":2070523,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must divide n.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":8000,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":2078524,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"True. If you can't form every element, then you'll only be able to form whatever is a common multiple of x and n","response_history":["I ","If you can't form ele","If you can't form el","If you can't form every elements,","If you can't form every elements","If you can't form every element, then y","TIf you can't  form eve ry element, then y","TrIf you can't form every element, then y","TruIf you can't form every element, then y","TrueIf you can't form every element, then y","True.If you can't form every element, then y","True. If you can't form every element, then you'll only be able to form whatever is possible by adding x over ","True. If you can't form every element, then you'll only be able to form whatever is possi","True. If you can't form every element, then you'll only be able to form whatever is a common de","True. If you can't form every element, then you'll only be able to form whatever is a common d","True. If you can't form every element, then you'll only be able to form whatever is a common multiple of x and n"],"rt":494141,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":2572667,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? ","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Always","response_history":["Always"],"rt":9729,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":2582402,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"Sometimes (I just realized after choosing always). If x +n x is odd (and n is even), then it should be able to form every element. It won't otherwise, I think","response_history":["Never.","Never (I just realized after choosing always). x + X","Never (I just realized after choosing always). x + x is always going ot","Never (I just realized after choosing always). x + x is always going o","Never (I just realized after choosi ng alway s). x + x is always going t","S (I just realized after choosing always). x + x is always going t","So (I just realized after choosing always). x + x is always going t","Some (I just realized after choosing always). x + x is always going t","Someti (I just realized after choosing always). x + x is always going t","Sometim (I just realized after choosing always). x + x is always going t","Sometime (I just realized after choosing always). x + x is always going t","Sometimes (I just realized after choosing always). x + x is always going t","Sometimes (I just realized after choosing always). If the result ","Sometimes (I just realized after choosing always). If t","Sometimes (I just realized after choosing always). If x +n x is odd, then ","Sometimes (I just realized after choosing always). If x +n x is odd, then","Sometimes (I just realized after choosing always). If x +n x is odd, the","Sometimes (I just realized after choosing always). If x +n x is odd, th","Sometimes (I just  realized  after choosing always). If x +n x is odd, t","Sometimes (I just realized after choosing always). If x +n x is odd, ","Sometimes (I just realized after choosing always). If x +n x is odd,","Sometimes (I just realized after choosing always). If x +n x is odd (and n is even), then it should be able to form every element. It won't otherwise, I think"],"rt":870232,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":3452637,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":11691,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":3464331,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your  backgrou nd. Please press \"Continue\" to continue.","rt":1430,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":3465762,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"25","response_history":["25"],"rt":2671,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":3468434,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Bachelors Degree","response_history":["Bachelors Degree"],"rt":2682,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":3471117,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanc ed math  class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Integral calculus","response_history":["Integral calculus"],"rt":12852,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":3483970,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":10455,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":3494426,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"How fa miliar a re you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"4 - used it but not often or recently","response_history":["4 - used it but not often or recently"],"rt":4625,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":3499053,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","response_history":["2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"rt":3345,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":3502399,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in  this HIT ?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2332,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":3504733,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":1919,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":3506653,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","response_history":["Male"],"rt":1795,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":3508451,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is/are your n ative la nguage(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":5175,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":3513627,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":5349,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":3518979,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"","response_history":[],"rt":1382,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":3520362,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"}]